Downloaded from
YTS.MX
[grand orchestral fanfare
playing]
Official YIFY movies site:
YTS.MX
♪
PUSS:
Star light, star bright,
first star I see tonight,
I wish I may, I wish I might
have this wish I wish tonight.
Once upon a time,
a Wishing Star
fell from the sky.
Scorching a great woods black.
The Dark Forest was born,
the Wishing Star hidden
at its center,
filling it with new life,
and the legend of a single wish
locked away in the star,
waiting to be granted.
CROWD:
Puss in Boots!
Puss in Boots! Puss in Boots!
-Puss in Boots! Puss in Boots!
-[neck cracking]
-PUSS: Welcome to my fiesta!
-[cheering]
Make yourselves at home, yeah.
Come on, eat.
Drink up. [chuckles]
Hey! [speaks in Spanish]
Good to see you again.
[giggles, grunts]
Papa, he stepped on my face!
And we will never wash it again.
[cheering]
People of Cordova...
It's Del Mar.
-People of Del Mar...
-[cheering]
...accept this golden gift
from Puss in Boots.
-[cheering]
-Play a song!
No, no, no. I couldn't.
-Sing, Puss, sing!
-[moos]
Nah, I couldn't possibly...
-[playing lively guitar melody]
-[cheering]
♪ Who is your favorite
fearless hero? ♪
♪ Fearless hero?
♪ Who's brave and ready
for trouble? ♪
-♪ You are, you are
-PUSS: ♪ Uh-huh!
♪ Who's so
unbelievably humble? ♪
♪ You are, you are
♪ Who is your favorite
fearless hero? ♪
-♪ Fearless hero?
-[grunts] -[laughs]
♪ Who's the...
[sings in Spanish]
♪ Who rolls the dice
♪ And gambles with his life?
♪ Who's never been touched
by a blade? ♪
♪ Puss in Boots
is never afraid ♪
[cheering]
♪ Who is your favorite
fearless hero? ♪
♪ Fearless hero?
-[screeches]
-[Puss laughing]
[whooping]
[exclaims in Spanish]
[dramatic vocalizing]
[laughs] Yeah!
[clears throat]
[bleats]
[gasps] My clothes.
My wig.
[nickers]
My portrait!
♪
Oh.
[chuckling]:
Hey, Governor.
Uh, one second.
[portrait tearing]
The outlaw, Puss in Boots.
Welcome! [speaks in Spanish]
No. [speaks in Spanish]
-Arrest these filthy peasants
-[crowd exclaims]
and bring me the head
of Puss in Boots!
Hey! This is a party!
Where is the music?
♪ He's the blade of justice,
stands up against evil ♪
♪ Fighting for the people
♪ And he's very good-looking
♪ Who is your favorite
fearless hero? ♪
♪ Fearless hero?
-[grunting fiercely]
-♪ Puss in Boots
♪ Puss in Boots
Puss in Boots has never
been touched by a blade.
-♪ Never been touched
-But you?
-[yelps] Skin that cat!
-[laughter]
Governor, lighten up.
-[whooshing]
-[laughs]
[yelps]
[fireworks popping, whistling]
[growling]
[grunts, growls]
[yelps, grunts]
[laughing]
-Uh-oh.
-[yelling, grunting]
Silly guards,
dogpiles don't work on cats.
-[laughter]
-[rumbling]
[growling]
Holy... [speaks in Spanish]
You awoke the sleeping giant
of Del Mar!
[people screaming]
♪
BOY:
Giddyap!
Whee! I'm flying!
No, you are not flying.
I will save you!
Save me, too!
If it's convenient.
-You, launch me.
-[grunts]
And the rest of you,
play double time.
♪ Who is your favorite
fearless hero? ♪
-[grunts]
-♪ Who is your favorite
-[growls]
-♪ Fearless hero?
♪ Who is your favorite
fearless hero? ♪
♪ Fearless hero?
[all gasp]
[screams]
-Spanish Splinter.
-[cheering]
[groans, grunts]
[Puss speaks in Spanish]
[yowls]
Fear me, if you dare.
[cheering]
[bell clangs]
Yee-haw!
[laughing]
[whooping]
-Yeah!
-[cheering]
[whooping]
[roars, grunts]
Hey, giant!
Pray for mercy from...
Puss in Boots!
[bell clangs]
Hey, you want to see
something cool?
-[grunts]
-[bell clangs]
-[whooping]
-[giant groans]
-[bell clangs]
-[cheering]
[speaks in Spanish] Del Mar.
You have been great!
-Get home safely.
-[clucks]
-Good night.
-CROWD: Puss in Boots!
Puss in Boots! Puss in Boots!
Puss in Boots...
You're still here?
[cheering]
Okay, okay.
One more number.
I call this one
"The Legend Will Never Die..."
[bell clangs]
[crowd gasping]
BOY:
Puss in Boots!
♪
MAN:
Puss? Puss.
Puss in Boots.
[groaning softly]
[grunts]
Uh, where am I?
Not to worry.
You're in good hands.
My hands!
I am the village doctor.
I am also the village barber,
veterinarian,
dentist and witchfinder.
[coughing]
And in my professional opinion,
you need a wash,
a blowout and a little trim
around the hindquarters.
Uh...
That's my professional
barber opinion.
But, putting on my doctor's hat,
I think we need to run
a few tests.
All right. Reflexes.
-[Puss yowls]
-Catlike.
-Temperature.
-[growls, yelps]
-Now lift your tail and relax.
-[gasps]
Trust me, I run hot. Yep.
Then how about the latest
in modern medical technology?
-Leeches!
-[leech squeals]
To draw out the evil humors.
[hisses]
Suit yourself. More for me.
Uh, listen, Doctor.
Thanks for everything, you know,
but I am feeling great.
Strong, like a bull! You know?
Now, do you know a good place
to get some gazpacho?
Please. This is serious.
What is it?
Puss in Boots,
how do I say this?
You died. [blows]
Doctor, please.
Relax! I am Puss in Boots.
I laugh at death.
[laughs] You see?
And anyway, I am a cat.
I have nine lives.
And how many times
have you died already?
Uh... I don't know.
I never counted.
I am not really a math guy,
you know?
-[speaks in Spanish]
-Take it easy, Doctor.
Let's see, uh... [chuckles]
There was the running
of the bulls in Pamplona.
♪
[panting, speaks in Spanish]
-Do you like gazpacho?
-[bull bellows]
[laughing]: Guess it's not
your night, huh, fellas?
[dogs growling]
-[loud thump]
-[Puss yowls]
[slurring]:
I am telling you,
a cat always lands on his feet.
Watch.
No. Puss in Boots
doesn't need a spotter.
Watch. [grunts]
[screeches]
No need to pull into port.
This will revolutionize travel.
Watch.
Uh, excuse me.
Does this have shellfish in it?
Yes, sir.
Eh.
-[groans]
-[clattering]
Puss, I think you set
the oven too high.
I am a master of the baking.
Watch.
[Gingy screams]
And then there was
the giant today.
[bell clangs]
So, what is that?
Like, uh, uh, four?
That makes eight, Puss.
You are down to your last life.
My prescription:
no more adventures for you.
You need to retire.
Me? Retire?
[laughing]: Are you
the village comedian as well?
Puss, is there any safe place
you can go?
Any special someone
you can rely on
in this moment of need?
[chuckles] I am Puss in Boots,
loved by one and all.
Anyone in particular?
I mean, uh,
how could I possibly choose?
Mm-hmm.
This is the address
of Mama Luna.
She is a cat fancier,
always on the lookout
for a new lap cat.
-You will be safe there.
-Lap cat?
I am no lap cat, Doctor.
I am Puss in Boots!
Not anymore.
Barber's orders.
I mean, doctor's orders.
And remember, Puss,
death comes for us all.
Treat?
You've really got to work
on your bedside manner.
[laughs] I am Puss in Boots.
I am no one's lap cat.
That doctor is a quack
and a crazy man.
He should stick to cutting hair.
Last call...
[speaks in Spanish] Boots.
Another glass of cream.
Make it your heaviest.
Oh, I keep the heavy stuff
in the back.
[scoffs] "Retire."
You are too good-looking
to retire.
[whistling a tune]
[thunder rumbling]
Well, well.
If it isn't
Puss in Boots himself.
[chuckling]
In the flesh.
Uh, hey.
There's the famous hat,
the feather
and, of course, the boots.
My compliments to your cobbler.
[chuckling]
[clears throat] Thanks.
Uh, good to meet you, too.
Hey. I never do this,
but can I get your autograph?
Been following you
for a long time.
Sign right there.
[laughing]
Puss in Boots laughs
in the face of death,
bounty hunter.
So I've heard.
You will find your reward
does not come easily.
This I tell you.
Everyone thinks they'll be
the one to defeat me,
but no one's escaped me yet.
[sighs] All right.
-Let's get it over with.
-[neck cracking]
Fear me, if you da...
♪
Okay, no more messing around.
[grunts]
-[Puss grunting]
-Slow. Sloppy. Sad.
[chuckling]
[growls, yelps]
[yells]
[whispers]: You're not
living up to the legend...
[speaks in Spanish]
[straining]
[grunts]
[grunting]
[panting]
[gasps]
[sniffing]
[sighs]
I just love the smell of fear.
[thunder crashes]
[heartbeat thumping]
What's the matter?
Lives flashing before your eyes?
Pick it up.
[grunts]
[whistling a tune]
[panting heavily]
-[whimpering softly]
-[footsteps]
[whistling continues]
♪
[speaking in Spanish]
[grunts]
[gasps]
-[panting]
-[thunder rumbling]
[insects trilling]
♪
[singing in Spanish]
I am no longer worthy.
I'm sorry.
[thunder rumbling]
[sighs]
We are gathered here today
to say goodbye to Puss in Boots.
There are no words
to express such a loss.
Thank you.
But it would be a crime
not to try.
He was known across the land
by many names.
The Stabby Tabby.
[speaks in Spanish]
The... [speaks in Spanish]
Whisperer.
To some, an outlaw.
To more, a hero.
To all, a legend.
I was right.
Words were not enough.
But perhaps a song.
♪ Who is your favorite
fearless hero? ♪
[crying]:
♪ Who is your favorite
♪ Fearless hero?
♪ You were, you were.
[sobbing]
♪
[thunder rumbling]
[creaking]
[sighs]
MAMA LUNA: I told you
health department people,
there are no cats here!
Uh... [clears throat]
-Meow?
-[lock clicks]
[cats mewing]
-[gasps]
-MAMA LUNA: Oh!
You're not from
the health department, are you?
No, you're not.
We better get you inside
because, baby,
they are always watching.
I am Mama Luna,
and this is my home.
And now it's your home, too.
Your forever home. [chuckles]
[gulps]
Ow!
♪ Kitty gets a bath
♪ The kitty gets a bath
♪ Hi-ho the...
I bet you never even had a name.
But you know what, I have
thought of something perfect.
I shall call you...
-[bell jingles]
-...Pickles!
Brother cats, sister kitties,
meet your new roommate.
[giggles]
Say hello, Pickles.
Meow, eh?
[cats yowling, hissing]
Ooh.
What? Did I say something salty?
It's my second language.
[grunts] Stupid mittens.
Get off me.
♪ This is the end
-[sings in Spanish]
-[meows, growls]
-[growls]
-Oh, no.
-♪ This is the end
-[trickling]
[sings in Spanish]
[sighs, gasps]
This is a person potty, Pickles.
That's your potty.
-[cat grunting]
-[flies buzzing]
So this is where dignity
goes to die.
-[sings in Spanish]
-[cats meow]
[grunts, exclaims]
No, no way.
-♪ The end
-[food sizzling]
♪ I'll never...
-MAMA LUNA: Uh-uh-uh.
-[yowls]
-[sighs]
-[cats meowing, purring]
[sings in Spanish]
[continues in Spanish]
-[cats meows]
-PUSS: Meow.
-♪ Desperately in need
-[cats purring]
♪ Of some stranger's hand
♪ In a desperate land
♪ This is the end.
[sniffing]
-[cow bellows]
-[bell clanging]
[sniffing]
[growls]
You got the scent?
These are too small,
and these are too big.
But these ones...
these ones are just right.
[Goldi laughs]
Baby! Track that cat.
[sniffing]
[all meow]
[tail thumping]
[sighs] Do you mind?
I'm trying to eat here.
I mean, meow. Whatever.
Oh, sorry.
[gasps]
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
You're a talking cat?
I'm a talking cat.
Let's talk.
[sighs] I'd rather eat.
Oh, not a problem.
We can eat and talk
at the same time.
-[speaks in Spanish]
-[gasps]
[speaking in Spanish]
-I don't speak Spanish, either.
-[chuckles]
You're funny.
-Uh... okay. Good talk.
-Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hang on.
Pickles? Is that your name?
Me, I don't have a name
or a home.
So, I'm no expert, but you
don't look like a Pickles.
Well, you don't look like a cat.
[gasps] Okay, okay, okay.
Full disclosure: I'm not a cat.
-I'm a dog. [shushing]
-MAMA LUNA: Hi, Bon Bon.
Meow.
MAMA LUNA: Oh, Pickles has
a new girlfriend? Okay.
I live under the porch.
It can get a little lonely
down there.
It's mostly controlled by
the rats and the centipedes,
but I have my own little corner.
Congratulations.
I just come up here
for the food and the friends.
-[hisses viciously]
-Mostly... mostly the food.
Please don't tell anyone.
I need this.
I won't tell. I don't care.
So you'll keep my secret?
A secret between friends?
Just a secret.
It's funny-- despite all this
best friend bonding,
you're still a mystery to me,
Pickles.
What's your story?
My story...
-♪
-[bird screeching]
What are we looking at?
[horse neighs]
...is over.
[gasps] Oh, no.
Want to rub my belly?
Hmm?
What-what's happening?
-Rub.
-Hard pass.
Come on, rub.
I need the practice.
I'm gonna be
a therapy dog someday.
What the hell are you
talking about?
I'm glad you asked.
When people feel bad,
they can rub my belly.
It'll make 'em feel better.
Rub my belly.
-No. No.
-Come on, rub it.
-Not happening. No.
-Rub it.
Let me be clear.
I don't want to touch
your belly, okay?
Okey doke.
So, what do you want?
I want to be left alone.
♪
-[snoring]
-[cats purring softly]
♪
[sighs, screams]
Ugh, you're back.
Oh, I never left.
[creaking footsteps]
[sniffing]
The wolf. He found me.
-[roaring]
-[cats yowling]
[screams]
Hello, missus.
We're looking for a cat.
This cat.
We've got an offer for him.
What could they possibly want
to offer Puss in Boots?
-What's a Puss in Boots?
-Seriously?
I told you
health department people,
there are no cats here.
Make her talk.
[growling]
Excuse me, my darling.
We're looking for
the legendary Puss in Boots.
Have you perhaps... seen him?
Too soft.
Out with it, you old biddy,
or I'll have your guts
for garters.
[whimpers]
Too hard.
That was not just right.
Oi, Baby, sniff him out.
You don't tell me what to do.
Listen to your sister, Baby.
Oh, she's not my sister!
She's a fugitive orphan.
-Ow!
-She is your sister.
Do as she says.
Fine, but all I can smell
is cats' pee.
-[cats yowling]
-Everybody!
Get to the safe room,
just like we practiced!
Oi. She's leggin' it.
Follow me, children! Ow!
Give her the piano
treatment, Papa.
Oh! You think this is
the first time
I've been stuffed in a piano?
-[Goldi laughing]
-[plays discordantly]
-[plays lively tune]
-PAPA: Here we go!
♪ Roll out the barrel...
-Oh...
-GOLDI: Mama, focus, please.
[growls]
[cats screeching]
[screams]
Hey! There's cats everywhere!
So many cats! [screams]
Amateurs.
-I'll be outside.
-[yowls]
My cats can play
better than you.
♪ Now's the time
to roll out the barrel... ♪
Goldi, is this him?
GOLDI:
That's a dog in a cat costume.
-[chuckles]
-Oh, yeah.
Tricky little bugger.
How about this one?
He's a ginger.
[cat yowls]
Is that a joke?
You think this scruffy,
geriatric bag of bones
looks like a legend?
This is definitely not...
BABY:
Puss in Boots! I found him!
Puss in Boots, dead and buried.
-Dead? No, no, no, he can't be.
-[sniffing]
Yep. The nose never lies.
Well, that's that, then.
What say we go
and hibernate, huh?
-No.
-Ow!
The map is being
delivered tonight,
and we have one chance
to steal it.
Without it, we'll never find
the Wishing Star.
The Wishing Star.
It does exist.
That star has one wish to grant.
One wish?
Think of what
that could mean for us.
Nine lives. Yes!
Well, I don't see
why we needed to hire
Puss in Boots
in the first place.
Ugh. Because nobody steals
from Big Jack Horner.
No! Not Jack Horner.
Don't worry, love.
We'll get that wish somehow.
Thank you, Mama.
Yeah, because I've got a plan.
I can nick a map
as good as any old cat.
[laughs]
You've got a plan?
What? I'm smart, ain't I?
Ain't I, Papa?
PAPA: No, you ain't
well-fixed for brains.
Robbing Big Jack Horner--
very risky.
But that wish could get me
my lives back.
And my life back.
Goodbye, Pickles!
Oh, no, Pickles, you're leaving?
[speaks in Spanish]
Start digging.
Okay.
But if this Puss in Boots
is such a big deal,
maybe we shouldn't be
desecrating his grave.
No, I don't think he would mind,
because he...
...is me!
Oh. O-Okay.
Oh, yeah. Uh... [clears throat]
Normally, I have a sword.
It's like a whole thing,
you know?
Pickles, you're Puss in Boots?
Not yet, but I will be.
I'll come... [yelps]
-I'll come with you.
-Sorry... [speaks in Spanish]
Puss in Boots walks alone!
♪
GUARD:
Open the gates!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hands off the merchandise.
We got this.
Okay. Just get in and get out.
-Easy peasy.
-Lemon squeezy.
Aah! What are you doing here?
I brought you a sword.
That's not a sword.
That's a stick.
-It's a stick sword.
-Go home.
Well, my home is where
my friends are.
Again, not friends.
-Rub for luck?
-[scoffs]
I don't need luck for this.
I am a highly skilled
master cat thief.
Watch.
[Puss straining]
You got this.
[grunting]
Hmm. [smacking lips]
I pronounce this batch...
delicious.
Ship 'em out.
Mr. Horner.
The Serpent Sisters
got the goods.
Is it? Is it the map
to the Wishing Star?
Stop everything.
You two, come with me.
We must get this
to the trophy room.
You know, it took a lot
of murdering to get this map.
It all started...
Take it to the trophy room!
[thumping]
[grunts]
[tweets, squawks]
-What the...
-[door opens]
Wow. Look at all
the magic stuff.
Yes, I collect
enchanted objects,
magical icons,
bobbles and geegaws
and la-di-da and blah-blah-blah.
JO: Check it out.
I'm walking on a magic carpet.
-Sweet.
-[high-pitched shouting]
The shrunken ship
of the Lilliputians.
Shut up!
Are those unicorn horns?
Baby unicorn horns.
Half as heavy, twice as sharp.
-Savage.
-[groans] They're trinkets.
They're nothing compared
to the awesome power
of the magic Wishing Star.
Speaking of which,
make with the box, sister.
JO:
You got it, boss.
Like I was saying,
the amount of murdering we...
Make with the box!
After so many years
of searching,
this is my moment.
With this wish,
I will finally be
the master of all magic.
JO:
Hey, Little Jack.
Excuse me?
-Could you do the thumb thing?
-Shh.
Like in the fairy tale?
It wasn't a fairy tale!
It was only a nursery rhyme.
[laughing]:
Oh, yeah. The lame one.
Little Jack Horner
sat in the corner
eating a Horner pie...
♪ Stuck in my thumb,
pulled out a plum ♪
♪ And said,
"What a good boy am I." ♪
[panting]
Look! A magic puppet.
♪ 'Cause I'm a real boy
♪ No strings attached.
-[cheering]
-Thank you. Thank you.
What's impressive?
I've been a boy the whole time.
[yells]
Little Jack Horner
didn't have any magic.
He was a pathetic,
buttered baker's boy.
Little Jack's dead!
I'm Big Jack Horner.
JAN:
Uh, Mr. Big Jack Horner, sir...
-[chuckles]: I barely know her.
-JO: What do you mean?
We're sisters, you goof.
We got matching face tattoos.
Easy peasy, lemon squeezy.
[Puss yelps, groans]
-Puss?
-Kitty?
-Puss...
-Kitty!
[grunts]
This is my job.
No, this is my job.
I'm double-crossing the bears.
No, I am double-crossing
the bears.
They tried to hire me
earlier today.
Well, they tried to hire me
two weeks ago.
That makes you plan B.
-[gasps]
-JACK HORNER: Aha!
-There it is.
-Whew.
Now, about your payment.
Hold up. You promised us
our weight in gold.
I did, didn't I?
Ever hear of the Midas touch?
Ah, cool. Dibs. [chuckles]
Oh, no.
I misjudged the situation.
[gasps]
This is why you don't cross
Jack Horner.
What is this?
-Are you a pirate now?
-Shh.
It's like a possum crawled
on your face and died.
-Shh!
-Of shame.
Please, mock me quietly.
I hate it. It's disgusting.
Well, I love it.
It's distinguished.
[deep creaking]
[screaming]
[wheezing]
Great plan, Baby. Real catlike.
Uh, can I go?
Pleasure doing, uh...
-Puss in Boots?
-Goldi. Bears.
-[speaks in Spanish] Jack.
-Kitty Softpaws.
My, you have a lot of nerve
coming back here.
Please. I was the best thief
you ever hired.
-You robbed me.
-You set me up.
You said you were going
on some spiritual retreat.
Namaste.
And you're supposed to be dead.
I got better?
Ugh. Just give us the map.
-And throw in a dozen pies.
-Eh?
Ooh. Have you got
any savory pies?
-What? N-No.
-Yeah, what flavors you got?
MAMA: Can we get all of that
in a bag to go?
Oh, would you stop talking
about blooming pies? Focus!
-[high-pitched screaming]
-Hand over that map,
or I'll punch holes
in the lot of ya.
[creaking]
-Oh, bums.
-Look out! It's coming down!
PUSS:
Ha!
I hate talking
fairy tale animals!
[screaming]
-[laughs]
-What? Get back here!
The best thief has won.
-Huh?
-KITTY: You're right.
-[Puss groans]
-She did.
Oh, come on!
-[yells]
-[roaring]
There. They're getting away.
♪
[henchmen yelling]
[distorted groaning]
-[screams]
-Ooh.
No, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no!
Nice catching up with you, Puss.
Got to go.
Here, kitty, kitty.
Is that a stick? What are you
gonna do with that...
-Ow!
-Ow! Me knuckles!
You shouldn't have
done that, mate.
[chuckles]
[screaming]
This idiot.
Hey, Puss.
I found a sandwich in here.
I think it's tuna fish.
-Drive... [speaks in Spanish]
-Okey doke.
-[neighing]
-[henchmen shouting]
Oh, cool.
Another member of the team.
BOTH:
We are not a team.
-Eyes on the road!
-Whoa!
Who is this guy?
-I'm Puss's best friend.
-No, he isn't.
And his therapy dog.
Definitely not.
Finally. You need therapy.
Give me the map. Trust me.
Trust you?
Like I did in Santa Coloma?
Really? Santa Coloma?
[speaks in Spanish]
Santa Coloma.
-Mine!
-[screeches]: Mine!
[both screeching, hissing]
[both blow, growl]
Hyah!
[gasping, cheering]
[neighing]
Good people,
accept this golden gift
from Puss in Boots!
[cheering]
[wolf whistling]
-Speed up! Go, go, go!
-[yells]
Assemble the Baker's Dozen.
-Careful with this.
-[yells]
I'll take this and that.
Oh, and these. One of those.
And I got to take that.
Yes. Yes.
No. Yes! Oh, yeah!
[humming a jolly tune]
All of these!
[chuckles] This one is right.
[bowling pins crashing]
[yells]
-[horses neighing]
-[yelling]
I'll get you, my kitties,
and your little dog, too.
[panting]
What? This is blank.
We've been ripped off!
Where is the...
Oh. Yeah.
I knew it was gonna do that.
"The Dark Forest
is deep and far.
Within its bounds,
you'll find the star."
[sighs] The Dark Forest?
No one goes
into the Dark Forest.
Or comes out.
KITTY: "A single wish
burns true and bright.
This map's the key,
so hold on tight."
[grunts, speaks in Spanish]
-You let go.
-A stick?
[chuckles]
What happened to your sword?
Got rid of it, you know.
Made things too easy.
I needed a challenge.
Yeah, you looked
pretty challenged back there.
[chuckles]
There's no way I'm letting you
hold the map.
Well, there's no way
I'm letting you hold the map.
-I can hold it.
-[whip cracking sound effects]
Yeah, right.
What's your deal, anyway?
You run with the Chihuahua Gang?
I don't think so.
-I don't believe you.
-That's okay.
As long as you believe
in yourself.
Wha...
Is he deranged?
-Yep.
-What's your name?
Oh, I've been called
all kinds of things.
Dog, Bad Dog, Stupid Dog.
Hey You! You There! Get Out!
Leave It! Drop It!
Big Rat, Small Pig, Rat Face,
Butt Nugget, [bleep] for Brains.
You know, that sort of thing.
But I've never had a name
that really stuck, you know?
That belonged to me.
-Is he done?
-And you are?
Softpaws.
Kitty Softpaws.
Wow. Yeah.
Now, that's a good name.
There's music
in a name like that.
Kitty Softpaws.
Nice try. Classic con.
No one's that dumb.
No one's that nice.
I don't trust you.
Me, neither.
He cannot be trusted.
But I trust him
more than I trust you.
PUSS: Wow.
This trip is going to be fun.
[horse neighing]
[sniffing]
♪
[thunder crashing]
This must be the Dark Forest.
Oh, my God!
It's gone.
It's back.
[speaking in Spanish]
Nothing to worry about.
[chuckles]
We step through as one.
Ready?
One, two, after you.
Wait, what? [screams]
Dog? Still alive?
-Let's go find out.
-Wait!
[all screaming]
Um... [clears throat]
-Whoa.
-Wow.
For a Dark Forest,
this place is pretty colorful.
I wish I had
my quinceañera here.
The Wishing Star is
in here somewhere.
Kitty, may I please see the map?
-No.
-Seriously!
You won't let me hold it
for even one minute?
Nope. Not even for one second.
Come on, Kitty.
You've got to trust me.
Wait. Wh-Wh-What's...
What's going on with his eyes?
Oh, they're getting bigger.
Oh, Kitty!
You got to trust him.
Look at those eyes.
Really? You call that cute?
[dog gasps]
Oh, look at her!
Those eyes are even bigger
than yours.
Do whatever she wants, Puss.
Wait a second. So poofy!
-No. With the paws?
-[purring]
Come on. [gasps]
With the hat?
It's all so cute!
Cuteness overload!
Can we look at the map now?
[whimpers]
KITTY:
"Follow this enchanted chart.
It knows your path
and knows your heart."
PUSS:
Is that us?
[rumbling]
It says we must go through
the Valley of Incineration
over Undertaker Ridge,
through the Cave of Lost Souls?
-Really? [screams]
-Let me take a look.
[rumbling]
What?
Swamp of Infinite Sorrows?
Mountains of Misery?
The Abyss of Eternal Loneliness?
There's something wrong
with this map.
I guess there is a different
terrible path for everyone.
It's almost like the forest
doesn't want anyone
to make a wish.
Well, I don't even have a wish,
but can I try?
Oh, mine says... [gasps]
We skip through
the Pocket Full of Posies.
-What?
-Huh?
Then drift down
the River of Relaxation.
-That sounds fun.
-No fair.
Why does he get the good one?
Wander the Fields
of Quick and Easy Solutions,
and arrive at the star.
Oh, wow! That sounds wonderful.
Oh, but no. This is your quest.
I don't want to impose.
-BOTH: You hold the map.
-[gasps] Really?
But don't you cross me,
or your name will be...
[speaks in Spanish]
Okey dokey.
Wait. Is that...
[screaming]
It's raining bears. Time to go.
-[sniffing]
-GOLDI: Oh, I'm tellin' ya,
when we get that wish,
it will make everything
just right for all of us.
Will it make us rich?
Rich enough to hibernate
all the year round?
The richest.
Will we be, like,
big-time thieves?
-The biggest.
-[chuckling]
Eh, you know that suit
Jack Horner wears?
-Yeah.
-I'm going to have one of them.
-Yeah?
-Only mine will be purpler.
-Like, twice as purpler.
-The purplest!
[chuckling]:
Nice.
Big-time thieves coming through!
-PAPA: I'll race ya!
-You can't beat me, old man!
What kind of wish
can do all that, Goldi?
Oh, I can't tell ya.
If you say what your wish is,
then it don't come true.
Sorry. Birthday wish rules.
Oh, come on.
Mother-daughter secret?
Mama, just drop it, please.
Oh. Oh, okay.
Hey, come on.
We've got some cats to catch.
♪
DOG: Birthday wish rules?
What's that mean?
It means I am not
telling you my wish.
He doesn't want to tell us,
because it's something stupid.
Like conditioner
for that thing on his face.
It's distinguished.
What about you, Kitty?
What are you gonna wish for?
Can't tell you.
Birthday wish rules or whatever.
Ha! I bet your wish
is something stupid like...
[grunts]
-[gasping]
-[Kitty laughs]
You're such a...
[Kitty yowling]
[gasps] This must be
the Pocket Full of Posies.
[grunting, gasping]
Out of the way, demon flower.
It's pruning time!
[yelling, grunting]
-[Kitty yelling in Spanish]
-[sniffs]
[flower squeals]
Aw, thank you.
[both screaming]
-We don't have time for this.
-[speaks in Spanish]
I thought your path was
supposed to be easy.
-[sniffs]
-[flower squeals]
You know, I think
all you have to do
is stop and smell the roses.
Seriously? [groans]
[both sniff]
This is stupid.
-All I smell is bull...
-Shh.
Watch.
[sniffs, exhales]
[Kitty and Puss scream, grunt]
Don't rush through it.
Take your time
and really appreciate
what's right in front of you.
[sniffs]
[flowers squeal]
KITTY:
Ugh. His path is so corny.
-Gracias.
-And cheesy.
-And lame.
-And weird, like him.
Yeah. Why are you
so ridiculous, dog?
What's your story?
My story? Oh.
It's actually
a very funny story. [laughs]
Back when I was a pup,
me and my littermates lived
with a family.
A family full of pranksters
who liked to play hide-and-seek,
and I was always it.
Pick on the little guy,
am I right? [sniffs]
They tried putting me in
a packing crate, a dumpster.
No matter how hard they tried,
I'd always find them.
So, one day, they get creative
and they put me in a sock
with a rock in it.
[laughs]
And then throw me in a river.
I gnawed a hole in the sock,
and I swam to the surface.
Never found them
or my littermates.
So I guess I'm still it.
-[laughs]
-Wow.
That is the saddest
funny story I've ever heard.
Well, joke's on them.
That sock they put me in,
I grew into it.
So, I got a great story
and a free sweater out of it.
Win-win.
Dude, you didn't win.
You of all people
should have a wish.
I already have a comfy sweater
and two best friends.
I got everything
I could wish for.
-No magic required.
-[Puss scoffs]
Hmm?
-[all sniff]
-[flowers squealing]
DOG:
Oh, lovely.
♪
[sniffing]
Oh, we're getting really close.
I can smell two cats,
a dog and... [sniffs] pie?
Well, if it isn't the idiots
who tried to steal from me.
Hey, he remembers us.
Behold, Excali...
Excali...
[grunts] Excalibur!
Yeah, I couldn't get
this rock off of it,
but still pretty cool, right?
MAMA:
He's gaining on us!
JACK HORNER:
Okay, little left.
That's it!
-Go faster!
-Whoa, he's up me back door.
[yells]
[distorted yelling]
[distorted]:
Goldi!
-[yelling, grunting]
-[laughs]
-JACK HORNER: Oh, look!
-[horses neighing]
Well, start chopping!
On it! You don't
have to tell me twice.
I'm gonna chop the heck
out of this Ficus lyra...
Jerry, no!
Avenge me, Jack!
-Die, die, die!
-[yells]
-[yells, whoops]
-Nope.
Time to bring out the big guns.
[chuckling]:
Guess I overpacked.
Magic snacks.
Save those for later.
Ha! Pay dirt.
All right, magical locust,
defoliate.
Fly and feast.
Eat those flowers.
I-I'm not a magic locust.
Why, I'm not a locust at all.
What are you, then?
Some sort of demon grasshopper?
-A deadly fairy?
-[screaming]
Put a spell on the forest, then.
I-I don't cast spells.
-Well, what do you do?
-Well, I-I-I judge you.
I sit on your shoulder
and judge your actions
and the quality
of your character.
I'm your conscience.
I really did overpack.
-[screams]
-JACK HORNER: Whoa!
Help me, Jack! Help!
Aren't you gonna help him, Jack?
You're losing a lot of men.
I'm not really stressing
about the manpower.
I've got a bottomless bag
of magic weapons.
These babies are gonna
get me that wish
even after the whole team
is dead and gone.
Now, now, Jack,
as your conscience, I...
-[squawks]
-Oh, my word!
It's the noble phoenix.
She's the symbol of rebirth
and the eternal...
-[flame whooshing]
-Oh!
[laughing]
Pretty boss flamethrower, right?
I really have my work
cut out for me on this one.
JACK HORNER: Don't be near
where I'm flame-throwing.
[Puss chuckles]
PUSS:
Do your job, demon flowers.
Soon.
[groans]
Okay, Kitty,
I think I've got it now.
[straining]
-Trust me! [whimpers]
-KITTY: Easy, easy.
You're gonna give yourself
a hernia.
Here, one more time. Like this.
[echoing]:
Trust me.
Aw. But of course
I trust you and Puss,
even without the eyes.
Yeah? Big mistake.
What do you mean?
You're my friends.
You know what trust gets you?
A sock, a rock
and a swim in the river.
You have to trust
somebody, right?
Not me. Uh-uh.
Whenever I've let my guard down,
I've been double-crossed,
declawed, played and betrayed.
Never again.
I am a solo act.
I keep my secrets,
and I play my cards close.
That's how you get
a winning hand.
Take it from me.
Never trust anyone.
W-Wait.
That's amazing. [gasps]
You're good.
[clears throat]
Kitty, I've been thinking.
Ugh, thinking about what?
My beautiful beard.
It is very distinguished, yes,
but it does deprive the world
a good look at, uh, the face.
So, if it will make you happy,
I could be convinced to...
-I've gotten used to it.
-Wait, what?
The beard-- keep it.
Uh, well, you see, uh...
[chuckles, sobs]
Kitty, please,
get this itchy thing off of me!
It's like a fever on my face!
Hold on. Is the great
Puss in Boots asking for help?
[speaks in Spanish]
Help. You were right.
-The beard is disgusting.
-And?
And it's like a possum
crawled on my face.
And?
And died of shame.
Okay, okay, possum face.
-I won't make you beg.
-[grunts]
Ow! [grunts]
Hey, slow down. Oh!
Go with the grain.
You got to go with the grain.
-I know what I'm doing.
-Hey!
I'm a master of the blade.
Right... [speaks in Spanish]
-[laughing]
-What? What? What's funny?
-Nothing should be funny.
-KITTY: Shh. [speaks in Spanish]
Ah, there's that handsome face
I remember.
The face I haven't seen since...
-Hey!
-...Santa Coloma.
Ah, yes. Santa Coloma.
You had it coming.
Here. You can have my...
[speaks in Spanish] blade.
Thank you.
Better than a stick.
[speaks in Spanish]
Stick sword.
[yelps]
-[yapping]
-[speaks in Spanish]
What are you doing?
[speaks in Spanish, whistles]
Where did that crazy dog go?
[singsongy]:
I think you like him.
No. No, I don't.
[singsongy]: I think
you're ready to name him.
No, I just need his easy path
to get my wish.
You mean my wish.
JACK HORNER:
You mean my wish!
Sorry.
[horses neighing]
[Baker's Dozen
grunting fiercely]
-The Baker's Dozen.
-Let him go.
Oh, I don't know.
I might keep him.
Would you like a treat?
Nice granny bag, Little Jack.
It's not a granny bag.
It is a magic nanny bag.
Now, make with the map,
or we'll see what
the unicorn horn really does.
-[whimpers]
-[Puss gasps]
Y-Y-You're not gonna shoot
a puppy, are you, Jack?
Yeah, in the face. Why?
-[yelling]
-What the...
Give us the map, or else
-the baker man gets it.
-BABY: Yeah!
I don't even have the map,
Little Bo Creep.
[yells, grunts]
Stop throwing my men at me!
-[screams]
-Come here!
Puss in Boots has the map!
-Let's get him!
-[Goldi yelling]
[all yelling]
-[gulps]
-I've got a plan.
First one to the dog
gets the wish! [yells]
What?
Oh, come on!
[yelling]
[distorted grunting]
[laughs]
-[grunts fiercely]
-[gasps]
[yowls]
-[growls]
-[screaming]
Steady.
[yelling, grunting]
-Whoa!
-[gasps]
[noisemaker blares]
[spits] What?
[laughing]
So that's what they do. Cool.
No! Not cool.
Ah, you shot me.
[noisemaker blares]
Ah, the sight's off.
[sneezes]
-I got him, Mr. Horner!
-JACK HORNER: My bad.
Oh, no.
[high-pitched ringing]
[muffled thudding]
[wolf whistling]
[heart thumping rapidly]
[gasps]
Puss, wait!
-[speaks in Spanish]
-[grunts]
Thanks for the map, Softpaws.
-[gasps]
-[rumbling]
-No, no, no!
-No!
Oi! You've just been crimed
by the Three Bears Crime Family.
-Yeah!
-So long, you plonkers!
[speaking in Spanish]
[groans] Puss, where are you?
[panting]
[screams]
Puss? Puss?
[gasps] Puss!
-[panting]
-[heart thumping rapidly]
Puss.
[muffled]:
What's wrong?
[heartbeat and panting
slowing down]
♪
[taking slow, deep breaths]
[sighs]
Thank you... [speaks in Spanish]
What's going on with you, Puss?
I...
I am down to my last life.
And, uh, I...
I am afraid.
Well, it's okay to be afraid.
No, not for Puss in Boots.
I-I'm supposed to be
a fearless hero.
A legend.
But without lives to spare,
I am nothing.
I need that wish
to get my lives back.
You should tell Kitty.
-She would understa...
-No, no, no, no.
She cannot hear of this.
Okay.
[groans]
[speaks in Spanish]
PUSS:
Kitty will never trust me again.
Not after Santa Coloma.
But that's just one bad heist.
Santa Coloma wasn't a heist...
[speaks in Spanish]
It was a church,
with a priest and guests.
-And Kitty.
-[bell tolls]
Everything but me.
I ran away then, too.
Oh. Oh.
[gasps] Oh!
You left her at the altar?
It was wrong. I know.
I am ashamed.
I just wish I hadn't
hurt her so badly.
I regret that day.
So, maybe you should
tell that to Kitty.
Might make you feel better.
Might make her feel better, too.
Puss! Dog!
Oh, there you are.
What happened back there?
Kitty. I lost the map.
I messed up.
We'll get it back.
We've been in worse pickles.
[grunts]
Who told you that name?
What name?
Uh, nothing.
The bears! We have to find them
before they find the star.
GOLDI:
Oh! We are so close.
It's finally happening.
I can taste that wish now.
And you know
what it tastes like?
-Pies?
-♪ Pies
♪ Who ate all the pies?
Who ate all the pies? ♪
♪ We did, we did,
we did, we did ♪
♪ We ate all the pies.
-[laughter]
-Oh, it's gonna be wicked.
Yeah. Imagine us,
a big-time crime syndicate.
Not a big-time
crime syndicate, love.
A big-time crime family.
Isn't that right, Goldi?
-Goldi?
-What?
Whoa! Hey, look,
the map is going all fizzly.
BABY:
What did you do?
-Give it me. No, no, no, no.
-Hey!
-[Goldi growls]
-[Baby yells]
BABY:
Goldi, no biting!
-[pained yelling]
-[Goldi sighs]
You're the smash, I'm the grab.
I hold the map.
-You got it?
-[choking]: Okay!
[grunts]
GOLDI: "To find your wish,
adjust your view.
What you seek
may be right in front of you."
Well, that's a load of rubbish.
What's that supposed to mean?
[gasps]
BABY:
Right in front of us.
MAMA: It looks like
our cabin back home.
GOLDI:
You really think our cabin
is in the middle
of the Dark Forest?
Baby, give it
the old sniff test.
[sniffs] Something's cooking.
-[Papa and Baby chuckling]
-No.
Do not open that door.
-[Mama gasps]
-We are home! Hello, door.
Oh, no, don't go insi...
[groans]
Maybe just a quick pop in.
-Hello, chairs.
-What say we hibernate?
Hello, honey.
Hello, my old friend.
I have missed you so...
[snoring]
Look, Goldi. Porridge. [sniffs]
And it's made
just the way you like it.
No matter how you make it,
she doesn't like it.
Stop it, all of you.
Maybe our wishes
have been granted.
Just stop.
It's not our wish granted.
It's an obstacle.
It's the forest playing tricks.
This isn't real.
None of this is...
Aw. That was your favorite book.
You used to stare at it
for hours.
[young Goldi humming a tune]
[gasps]
[laughing]
[grunts]
Too hard.
[grunts] Whoop!
[chuckles]
Too soft.
[grunting]
Just right.
Oh, this was it.
What was it, Mama?
The day a little orphan girl
broke into our cabin
and stole our hearts.
[yelps, whimpers]
The day when our world
became just right.
How's it going?
Can you see anything up there?
Not yet...
[speaks in Spanish, yells]
-You okay?
-[speaks in Spanish] I am good.
[chuckling]:
So good.
[screams, grunts]
[panting]
If you wanted to hold my hand,
all you had to do is ask.
Uh, just, uh,
feel free to pull me up
whenever you get a chance.
Oh, I was just remembering
the last time
I offered you my hand.
Only, that time,
I believe you had cold feet.
[chuckles]
Kitty...
[sighs]
About that day.
Puss in Boots is not
supposed to be afraid.
But outside that church
in Santa Coloma,
that was the first time
I ever felt fear.
So I ran.
It was a mistake, Kitty.
It's okay.
-No, no. It was cowardly.
-It's okay.
-You alone at the altar.
-Puss.
In your beautiful,
poofy wedding dress.
Puss! It's okay.
I didn't show up, either.
Wait, what?
What do you mean,
you didn't show up?
Well, I knew
I could never compete
with your one true love.
-Who?
-Yourself.
The legend.
Uh...
I wasn't gonna show up
for that guy.
But you don't seem
like that guy anymore.
Everything okay up there?
I'm giving you a thumbs-up,
just so you know.
KITTY:
Puss!
Look.
What do you think, bug?
Do I wait for the cats to steal
the map and then kill them,
or do I just kill everybody
all at once?
You know, I'm starting to think
you don't appreciate
the value of a life.
What? No.
I mean, I love these guys.
[screaming, groaning]
Flex the glutes.
I need a solid surface.
There's good in all people.
You know, Jack, maybe we need
to dig a little deeper.
T-Tell me about your childhood.
[sighs]
You know,
I never had much as a kid.
Just loving parents
and stability and a mansion
and a thriving baked goods
enterprise for me to inherit.
Useless crap like that.
But once I get my wish,
I'll finally have the one thing
that will make me happy.
Oh, well, what's that?
All of the magic in the world.
-[laughing maniacally]
-For me.
And no one else gets any.
-Is that so much?
-Yes!
Agree to disagree.
All right, bring it over.
-[horses neighing]
-[yelling, groaning]
[screaming]
Help!
Sweet Mother of Goose, Jack!
Well, you know what they say.
Can't bake a pie
without losing a dozen men.
-[chuckles]
-Oh. Oh!
That was horrible.
Your wish is horrible.
You're horrible!
You're an irredeemable monster!
Oh, oh.
What took you so long, idiot?
[screams]
[sighs]
You're not chatty, are you?
Mm-mm.
Okay, you take the window,
I'll take the chimney.
What do I take?
Oh, you take it easy, Perrito.
We need you
to stay here and, uh...
-Uh, uh, guard our rear.
-Yeah. Yeah.
On your six. Got your rears
eyeballed and covered.
Hands in, crew.
Ready?
Go, Team Friendship!
Team Friendship?
I did not agree to this.
Yeah, do better. Try harder.
Well, just a placeholder name,
you know.
I'll workshop it, okay?
-Go get 'em, tiger.
-Hey!
-Take it easy.
-[Kitty chuckling]
[snoring]
Ready to get our wish back?
"Our wish"?
Well, I've been thinking,
if you play your cards right,
maybe we could share the wish.
Share the wish.
[snoring]
[grunts]
[chuckles, yelps]
[sighs]
[gasps] It's gone!
-[screams]
-Wake up.
Someone's nicked the map.
What's all this?
What's all this bother about?
Oi! Did you not hear her?
The map is missing.
Somebody took it.
[speaks in Spanish]
Oi! You criming us
when we just crimed you?
No, no crime-backs.
Oh, you're dead cat meat.
-[Goldi grunts]
-Okay, okay, okay.
It's all... yours!
Nowhere to go, Softpaws.
Really? Let's see
what the map has to say.
-[rumbling]
-No!
-Our cabin!
-BABY: My honey!
What the dickens?
Oh, no, you don't. [yells]
[gasps] Oh, no.
[all grunting]
[yelps, grunts]
-We're coming, Gol... [groans]
-I'll get it. I'll get it.
-Get off me, you big lump.
-Hold still.
Hold on! I'm coming, Team...
[screams]
[muffled yelling]
Sorry. Sorry. Sorry,
sorry, sorry!
[growling]
PUSS:
Uh-oh.
-Shall we dance? I'll lead.
-Huh? Wha...
Aah! Too hot!
Aah! Too cold! Brain freeze.
[grunts]
-Oh, that is just right.
-[yells]
[grunting]
Aye? What the...
♪
No!
[both yelling]
-GOLDI: Oi! Forget something?
-[both gasp]
[whimpering]
They got Perrito!
Don't worry,
we can track them with this.
Wait, stop!
-[rumbling]
-[screaming]
Puss, watch out!
Kitty!
Puss!
Look!
There, there they are.
Just out there.
You go get Perrito.
I'll find a way out of here.
♪
PUSS'S VOICE:
Puss.
Hey, good-looking.
[screams] What is that?
Why so jumpy...
[speaks in Spanish]
Whoa, what's happening?
Hello, Puss. Gazpacho?
Long time, no see.
Always a pleasure to see me.
[yowls]
[sings in Spanish]
♪ Number nine.
It's a proper party now that
all nine of us are here.
-Yeah!
-[speaks in Spanish] Fiesta!
You know what? [exhales]
[slurring]:
I love you guys.
So, you are my former lives?
Reflections of
the good old days.
Okay.
Back when we were
larger than life.
-A legend.
-We dance.
♪ We sing.
-We are strong.
-ALL: Like the bull.
[speaks in Spanish]
You remember this one?
♪ Who is your favorite
fearless hero? ♪
♪ Who is your
ALL:
♪ Favorite fearless hero?
PAPA: Well, that's it.
Game over, innit?
Them cats stole
the stolen map we stole,
and we ended up with
diddly-squat-- nothing.
Or maybe we could be happy
without a wish.
What are we doing?
They ain't coming back.
Goodbye, purple trousers.
Oh, they'll come back-- for him.
You're darn tootin'.
Puss and Kitty always rescue me
when I'm kidnapped--
which happens a lot--
'cause we're a team.
-Aw, that's lovely.
-Yep.
Team Friendship.
Ugh. No! That is a crap name.
Well, we're-we're...
we're still workshopping it.
Oh, them cats ain't gonna
risk their lives
for this daft little pup.
You're just saying that
because you want to eat 'im.
I do not. I just want
to pet him with my teeth.
Stop thinking about
your belly, Baby.
In fact, stop thinking, period.
You'll just hurt yourself,
you muppet.
[laughing]:
"Muppet."
And why would I listen to
a porridge-stealing orphan
like you?
-You're not even a bear.
-Zing!
[laughs] I'm more of a bear
than you are.
She got you.
You're nothing but
a low-rent Cinderella.
Oh!
Well, that's rich
coming from you, Baby,
'cause you know what you are?
Wait for it.
You're a daft, fat,
slow-thinking,
no-reading, Lyme-diseased,
flea-ridden dingleberry bear.
Boom!
I haven't got dingleberries.
No, you do. You do have 'em.
[laughing]:
Dingleberries!
Oi! You shut up,
you little mutt,
or I'll cut you
from pooper to snooter!
[gasps] I'm in the mix now.
Okay! Okay, here we go.
You're all a bunch
of knuckle-dragging,
honey-scrounging, grub [bleep],
oafish [bleep],
[bleep] munching,
mangy [bleep] nugget,
[bleep],
and your snooter! [laughs]
[laughs]
I like the cut of his jib.
Ah, this is great.
Razzin' and ribbin' and barbin'
and poopin' and snootin'.
Oh, I wish I had
a family like this. [sighs]
Speaking from one orphan
to another, Goldi,
you won the orphan lottery.
I like his jib as well.
-Let's keep him. [gasps]
-What?
PAPA:
Huh? Where'd he go?
-No! We said no crime-backs.
-No, Baby, wait!
Ow! Not the bees!
♪ The legend will never die...
-♪ Da-da-da-dun.
-Bravo!
[cheering, laughter]
One more number.
[chuckling]:
No, no, sorry, fellas.
This has been fun, huh?
Yeah, but could you tell me
how to get out of here?
I've got to get back
to Dog and Kitty.
Whoa! I thought you were going
to get the wish.
You got the map.
You don't need them.
Yeah, get those lives back.
Become the legend again,
town to town.
[crowd chanting
"Puss in Boots!"]
-Party to party.
-[jovial chatter, cheering]
Puss in Boots walks alone.
Yeah, Puss in Boots walks alone.
Was the legend so big there was
no room for anyone else?
Oh, the legend's still big...
[speaks in Spanish]
It's you that got small.
Yeah, you changed, man.
I hear he's best friends
with a dog now.
And he doesn't even
have a sword.
[laughs] Some hero.
You've become a scaredy-cat.
We should call him
Wuss in Boots.
-Ah, no, no, no, no.
-[laughter]
Didn't you hear?
His new name is Pickles.
-So lame.
-[laughter]
Where is your litter box,
Pickles?
You know what?
You guys are jerks.
Which is very conflicting
for me.
I'll find my own way out. Adios.
Oh, you think you are
better than us?
Without us, you will always
live a life of...
Fear.
You.
I do love the smell of fear.
[sniffs] It's intoxicating.
[hiccups] It is?
Sorry to crash the party
with your past lives.
[chuckling]:
Or your past deaths,
as I like to call them.
[echoing]: I was there
to witness all of them.
Each frivolous end.
But you didn't even notice me
because Puss in Boots laughs
in the face of death, right?
But you're not laughing now.
You are no bounty hunter.
You are...
Death.
And I don't mean it
metaphorically
or rhetorically or poetically
or theoretically
or in any other fancy way.
I'm Death, straight up.
And I've come for you,
Puss in Boots.
But I'm still alive.
[chuckles] You know...
[inhales sharply]
I'm not a cat person.
I find the very idea
of nine lives absurd.
And you didn't value
any of them.
So, why don't I do us
both a favor
and take this last one now?
That's cheating!
Shh. Don't tell.
Run, Puss in Boots!
-Make the wish!
-[gasps]
Go ahead, run for it.
Makes it more fun for me.
[growls]
♪
[panting]
-Run.
-[laughing]
[laughing continues]
-[growls]
-[screams]
Run.
-[laughing continues]
-Run.
Hey, Puss.
-[panting]
-WOLF: Run.
Puss! Puss, we're here!
Wh-Where's he going?
♪
GOLDI:
That's the third time
we've passed
that same rock, Baby.
Oh, not again.
What do you want me to do?
I've lost the scent.
You only have one job.
The one thing that makes you
mildly useful is your nose,
and apparently,
you can't even use that.
-Goldi.
-I'm starting to think
this wish isn't
what you promised us.
-Leave off, Baby.
-So, what is it, eh?
What's your "just right"?
What's so blasted important
that you've got us stranded
in this haunted forest?
I'm getting a family!
That's what.
A proper family.
Then everything
will be just right.
Your "just right"
is getting rid of us?
Well, I guess some people
just stick around
until the porridge is gone,
eh, Goldi?
Come on.
You didn't think
I would actually stay.
I'm not a bear.
[whooshing]
I was always afraid
it was too good to last.
And whether you think
we're your family or not,
if this is something
that will make you happy,
we'll get you that wish.
Come on, boys.
[chuckling]:
Oh, what a good boy am I.
"Star light, star bright,
"first star I see tonight,
I wish..."
I can't believe
I fell for it again.
Kitty, you don't understand.
Don't understand what?
That you've been playing me
this whole time?
I need this wish.
Oh, yeah? You want to know
what my wish was?
Someone, anyone I could trust.
Hey!
In my whole life,
I've never had that.
But I thought I finally found
that someone
without a wish.
I thought it was you.
But you're still running.
Still the same old
Puss in Boots.
But I am not!
I am not Puss in Boots.
I'm... [sighs]
I am on my last life.
I need to get my lives back.
Without them, I am not...
I-I am not...
What? The legend?
[chuckles]
I still can't compete
with your one true love.
Go on, get your lives back.
[grunts]
Just keep them out of mine.
[whimpering]
Kitty, Death is after me!
What?
JACK HORNER: I've been called
a lot of things...
but never Death.
I like it.
-That's my wish!
-MAMA: Oi!
That's Goldi's wish.
[growling]
♪
[growls]
[knuckles crack]
[yells]
[growls]
[all yelling]
PAPA:
Grab him!
JACK HORNER:
Move! Out of my way!
I've got it! I've got it!
Don't got it.
[all grunting]
JACK HORNER:
That's mine.
[whooshing, rumbling]
Bang, bang, bang!
[grunting]
Oh, come on.
You walked into that one.
[grunts, yelps]
Mr. Horner, I need your help!
Duly noted, but a little busy
at the moment.
Pew, pew!
Mr. Horner!
[growling]
[grunting]
[all grunting]
-[Kitty screeches]
-Ooh.
Aha! It's bear season.
[grunts]
Oi, I'm gonna bust you up,
plum thumb,
and then I'm gonna
wear your clothes.
That was weird.
[screams]
-[Jack Horner laughing]
-[whimpering]: No, no, no...
Baby!
-Mama, help!
-I got you!
-BABY: Papa!
-Son, I'm coming!
-Got you.
-Help!
-MAMA: Hold on!
-BABY: Something's happening!
Help me!
Help! No, no, no!
Hang on, son!
I can't stop it!
Mama, I'm slipping!
I'm slipping... [screams]
[screaming]
Like I told you, Baby,
you're the smash, I'm the grab.
Yes! Yes!
[grunts]
-[chuckles]
-PUSS: No!
[straining]
-[laughs]
-[Kitty yells]
[frustrated groan]
Hey, Softpaws,
how do you like these apples?
Die! Blow up already.
-Softpaws.
-[groans]
[yells]
[grunts] Okay.
Okay, you know, maybe it's time
to bury the hatchet!
[grunts]
Oh, I shouldn't have
telegraphed it!
[yaps]
Yeah, I don't know
what to do with this,
but if you think
you need those lives...
Thank you, Perrito.
You know,
I've only ever had one life,
but sharing it
with you and Kitty
has made it pretty special.
Maybe one life is enough.
-[wolf whistling]
-[gasps]
-Huh?
-What is that?
[whistling continues]
Who's that?
He's here for me.
[grunts] Puss!
I've enjoyed the chase...
[speaks in Spanish]
but I think we've reached
the end now, you and I.
You gonna take
the coward's way out?
Run away to more lives?
Or are you gonna fight?
Pick it up.
Go on, pick it up.
♪
WOLF:
What's the matter?
Lives flashing before your eyes?
No.
Just one.
I'm done running.
Fear me, if you dare.
[chuckles]
This is gonna be fun.
[snarls]
[grunts]
[Puss grunting]
[straining]
[speaking in Spanish]
[wolf clicking tongue]
You really got to stop
losing that.
[gasps]
[wolf grunts]
Say hello to my...
[speaks in Spanish] blade.
[grunting fiercely]
Come on!
-[grunts]
-[gasps]
Pick it up.
[sighs] I know I can never
defeat you, lobo,
but I will never stop fighting
for this life.
[growls]
[growls viciously]
[yells in frustration]
[speaking in Spanish]
[groans]
You're ruining this for me.
I came here for
an arrogant little legend
who thought he was immortal.
[sighs]
But I don't see him anymore.
[gasps softly]
♪
Live your life, Puss in Boots.
Live it well.
You know we will
meet again, right?
[speaking in Spanish]
[whistling]
[yipping, panting]
-[chuckles]
-KITTY: You know,
when you said
Death was after you,
I thought you were just
being melodramatic.
The wish is yours.
You deserve someone
you can trust.
I don't need it.
I've got what I wished for.
No magic required.
[rumbling]
[Jack Horner grunting]
[Jack Horner belches]
JACK HORNER:
Ah, magic snacks.
[both gasp]
[Jack Horner laughing
maniacally]
Holy... [speaks in Spanish]
I was worried for a second
I would come out naked,
but my clothes grew, too. Cool.
Thank you.
[both scream, grunt]
Gotcha.
The last wish.
It's mine.
"Star light, star bright,
-first star I see tonight..."
-[gasps]
[Puss shouts in Spanish]
"I wish I may, I wish I might
-have this wish..." Huh?
-[speaks in Spanish] Horner!
Please don't make that wish.
Please?
[straining]:
Wh-What are you doing?
Please...
Seriously, are you having
a hernia or something?
[straining]:
Pretty please...
They're such pools
of vulnerability.
[continues straining]
It's so cute...
how you think
that would work on me.
Don't you know I'm dead inside?
By the way,
your nose is bleeding.
Oh.
I was just buying some time
for Team Friendship.
[grunts]
Team what?
[yells]
[all groan]
BOTH:
Spanish Splinter!
Ow! [yelling in pain]
Hey!
What have you done? No!
The map. My wish.
MAMA:
Go, go, go!
Whoa!
[grunts]
It's mine.
[laughing]
Huh?
[stammering]:
You looking for something?
Consider this
my resignation, mister.
[squawks]
What?
[yelps]
What did I do to deserve this?
I mean, what specifically...?
[rumbling]
[whooshing]
[all oohing and aahing]
MAMA:
Gorgeous.
I hate to say it,
but should we make a wish?
Kitty, one life spent with you
is all that I could wish for.
BABY [crying]:
You saved my life, sis.
You was gonna make the wish,
but you didn't make the wish
'cause you wanted
to save your family.
-[shushing]
-And I-I was really scared.
And then... [sobbing]
Oi, don't get
so blubbery about it.
Whose porridge would I eat
otherwise?
I'm sorry you didn't get
your wish, Goldi, love.
But I did, Mama.
I did get my wish.
Everything...
is just right.
Oh.
Oh, now you've made me cry.
Aw.
Now, what say we all go home
and hibernate?
Hey, Goldi, you are a chip
off the old block, you are.
Well, what can I say?
I won the orphan lottery.
Softpaws, Boots.
-Goldi.
-Bears.
Hey, Baby, you got any ideas
for our next job?
Oh! Remember that pie factory?
I suspect that
they might be experiencing
a leadership vacuum.
[chuckling]:
Oh, family business.
Oh, how exciting.
Now's a good time to talk about
ethical business practices.
[screams] There's a talking
cockroach on my nose!
-Get it off! Get off!
-GOLDI: Hold still.
BUG:
Oh, no, no, wait just a second.
-[Goldi grunting]
-Ow! Hey! Hang on!
Hey, Perrito, about that name.
Let's pick one out for you.
Yeah. Oh, what about...
[speaks in Spanish]
-Hmm...
-Ah. "Chomper."
What do you think...
[speaks in Spanish]
"Chomper," no?
I got it, I got it.
How about "Jeff"?
-Jeff?
-Yeah.
He doesn't have a Jeff's face.
[chuckling]
You know,
if it's the same to you,
I think I'll just stick
with "Perrito."
I kind of like it,
since that's what
my friends call me.
-Then "Perrito" it shall be.
-[Puss chuckles softly]
PUSS: You know, to be honest,
"Chomper" is pretty good.
PERRITO:
Yeah, but no.
PUSS: Well, we'll keep,
uh, workshopping it.
[Puss chuckling]
GOVERNOR: I want this vacation
to be perfect!
Did you remember to pack
my captain's hat?
-Yes, Governor.
-[squawks]
And your captain's shoes,
your captain's coat
and your captain's pajamas.
And what about...
My boat!
Puss in Boots!
[panting]
PUSS:
Perrito!
Team Friendship?
We did not agree to this.
Yeah, it makes us
look ridiculous.
Too late now. It's official.
-[bird screeches]
-Aah! Seagull! Whoa.
[all yell]
Steady as she goes, Perrito.
Dokey doke.
Where are we headed, anyways?
Off to find new adventures
and to see some old friends.
["La Vida Es Una" by Karol G
playing]
[singing in Spanish]
♪ Oh-oh-oh
[continues in Spanish]
♪
♪ Oh-oh-oh
[continues in Spanish]
-[song ends]
-PUSS: Welcome to my fiesta!
["Fearless Hero" playing]
Puss in Boots!
[laughs, whoops]
To more, a hero.
To all, a legend.
♪ Who's brave
and ready for trouble? ♪
-♪ You are, you are
-Uh-huh!
♪ Who is so
unbelievably humble? ♪
-♪ You are, you are
-♪ Who's the
[sings in Spanish]
♪ Who rolls the dice?
♪ You are, you are
♪ And gambles with his life?
♪ Who is your favorite
fearless hero? ♪
♪ Fearless hero?
♪ Puss in Boots
[vocalizing]
Puss in Boots!
[laughs, whoops]
♪ He's the blade of justice
♪ To more, a hero
♪ Fighting for the people
♪ To all, a legend
♪ Puss in Boots
-♪ Puss in Boots?
-♪ Puss in Boots
Puss in Boots!
[vocalizing]
I love that song.
Bravo! [laughs]
-♪ Who's ready for trouble?
-♪ You are, you are
-♪ Who's unbelievably humble?
♪ Who's never been touched
by a blade? ♪
♪ You are, you are
♪ Puss in Boots
is never afraid ♪
♪ You are, you are
♪ Who is your favorite
fearless hero? ♪
♪ Fearless hero?
♪ Who is your favorite
fearless hero? ♪
♪ Fearless hero?
♪ Puss in Boots
[vocalizing]
♪ Who is your favorite
fearless hero? ♪
Puss in Boots!
[laughs, whoops]
♪ Puss in Boots
[vocalizing]
♪ Who is your favorite
fearless hero? ♪
[vocalizing]
[whooping, laughing]
[clears throat]
[song ends]
["Por Qué Te Vas"
by Gaby Moreno playing]
[singing in Spanish]
[continues in Spanish]
[song ends]
PUSS:
Oh, you're still here?
[chuckling]